One, I'm Stephen
because each author of this study is responsible
for the corresponding part. Not all authors
understand each other's contents, so.
We plan to hold an internal briefing on the study
today. I would like to talk about the study
I almost redesigned and finished during the inner
rebuttal period
and the topic is estimating divergent carbon
stocks and sinks. I've said approach.
Before start the presentation
I needed to make a confession. At that outset, here
a little over ten years ago
I did something that I regret
something that I'm not particularly proud of
but here I feel a kind of obliged to reveal. In the
late 2010s, in the moment of young indiscretion.
I went to a university. At that moment
I did not do very well in English exams
and was still like an idiot. I even thought
ignorant that machine learning should be a cool
science fiction technology, something that the.
But today, against my better judgment
I want to try to dust off some of those machine
learning skills. What's left of those machine
learning skills?
And I don't want to tell you complicated technical
details. I want to make a case. I want to make a
hard-headed.
Evidence-based for rethinking how we
conceptualize the knife-set approach and how we
estimate carbon sinks and stocks. And here is my
outline. I will review the proposed in
introduction and describe the knife-set
approach in materials and methods. And and then
discuss about some new findings and compare our
methods with IPCC's methods benchmark.
And make a conclusion
. Around two years ago
Kobayashi Sensei and I shared published research
articles with each others
and then we found one paper mentioned that
when the annual mean temperature was increased
and the above ground biomass of most of bamboo.
Was increased in Taiwan as well. However
it's totally different in Japan. He said. Hence
a question is formed
Is the phenomenon possibly like a carrying
capacities index
such as forest above ground biomass?
And we made an assumption as the figure
and there is a temperature period is suitable for
moss bamboos growing, like this figure.
Too hot or too cold will cause the above-ground
biomass of the moss bamboo to decrease. And after
that, we collect moss bamboo forest data from
Japan and Taiwan.
And the distribution of the biomass and the annual
mean temperature shows like the figures. And we
found that even though the assumption is
partially correct
it may have some hidden variables. It seeks behind
the phenomenal.
Because we also found a lot of observation themes
divergent, and if I added data from China and Korea
our assumption above is not easy to prove. So we
stuck on the assumption here. On the other hand.
The above assumption reminded me that Dr. Chen
Chaihui and I was trying to use regression model to
predict the mossel bamboo biomass and the carbon
stocks about seven years ago.
And this kind model has a good ability to evaluate
the aboveground biomass
but very awful in belowground part. And we cannot
solve the problem if the independent variables
and the dependent variables divergent on the
distribution at the moment. Perhaps it's
necessary to find a method for belowground carbon
sink and stocks.
And we want to build a model which can be used to
predict the dependent variables when the
independent variables are divergent and and
chaotic on the distribution in ecological
systems. So.
Previously, we was used my methods
which is a Gibbs sampling type Monte Carlo plus
linear regression and random forest methods to
impute the raw data set. Then
used the bidirectional stepwise regression
methods to build a series of linear regression
models and output the prediction.
However, the method contained some part of
produced data, which means if some factors are not
so have a higher explanation power
it perhaps caused a overfitting in the output. And
furthermore, after that, Richard and Simon.
And I build a hybrid method which combined time
series ARIMA and Gibbs sampling with random
forests to estimate the stock price
and is hence workable for estimating divergent
target variables in chaotic systems. That
experience led me to consider how about to use the
similar structure to estimate chaotic or
divergent variables.
Okay, so let's start today's
internal briefing
, and
for the first part.
What is necessary to investigate the biomass and
the mega carbon storage models in bamboo forests?
And I think because of land use changed
especially deforestation and agricultural
activities increase
energy consumption and the burning fossil fuels
which comes from the below ground
the greenhouse gas emission have skyrocketed
after the industrial revolution.
And the greenhouse effect has intensified
recently, and all above reasons are very likely
causing global warming
which is also inducing extreme weather and the
climate change, and the carbon stocks.
In vegetation is an important role in carbon cycle
which affects carbon dioxide to meet in the air on
Earth. And for combating the hard core problem
the United Nations Framework Convention on
Climate Change is adopted on the ninth of May in
nineteen ninety-two. And in the UNFCCC, a lot of.
Countries will arrange some policymakers to
attend their conference. Intergovernmental
Panel on Climate Change will provide scientific
reports and studies to the UNFCCC and help
policymakers to assist climate policy. So
forest carbon sink and stocks are also important
for policymakers to assist policies of
mitigation.
However, aometric model of carbon stock and sinks
of below ground in bamboo forests looks always low
accuracy. Why?
Before answering
we need to talk about the spatial characteristics
of bamboo. Here
we provide a case of Philostichus edulis
and bamboo forests are widely distributed in the
world.
For instance, you will find them in Asia, America
and Africa, but somehow.
Two years ago, I saw some planted bamboos in France
as well. Anyway
most of bamboo is a kind of temperate wood bamboo
and widely distributed in Eastern Asia. And
because of bamboo have no cambium
they will accumulate dry matters in the secondary
wall year by year. And after finish their growth at
the H one, they do not consumed.
Quite a lot carbonhydrate animal
and due to mature bamboos do not consume too much
carbonhydrate, carbonhydrate may transport to
other bamboos or shot, and so far.
Some study revealed that most of bamboos have a
resin system and can transport carbonhydrate and
nutrient to somewhere. This may be one of the main
reason that below ground biomass ANPP and BNP P are
divergent in bamboo forest. Okay
now we get back to the problem nowadays.
Of the climate change
and even though carbon storage in vegetation is an
important factor in carbon cycle
the method provided by IPCC's guideline is a
little bit rough
especially on estimated bamboo carbon stocks and
sequestration. So they just rely on one study from
Africa, and it's.
Parties of UNFCCC may use bodily forest data to
calculate the carbon stock and the sinks.
In bamboo forest
hence the purpose of this study is to investigate
biomass, carbon storage
and nutrient contents in soil of most of bamboo
forest, and to collect previous published
journal articles data
and to design a method combined linear regression
and random forest with skip sampling approach for
estimating carbon stocks and sinks in forest
and our study said.
Is in FFPRI Kansai Research Center in Japan
and the annual temperature is around the sixteen
point four Celsius degree
and the annual mean precipitation is one thousand
seven hundred and five millimeter per year
and the diapch is around the nine point seven
centimeters, and the high is nearly fifteen
meters. The cum density is.
Around nine thousand per hectare. Furthermore
the total biomass is one hundred and
eighty-six megagram per hectare. All of them are
larger than the average size in China, Korea
and Taiwan.
At the beginning of the series studies
we set study site at the sample plot in
investigation biomass
especially in above ground biomass and below
ground biomass
and then dried the samples and run elemental
analyzer to know the carbon ratio in biomass to
estimate the carbon stock and the sinks.
After we obtain the data for carbon stock and the
sequestration of most of bamboo forest in Japan
and Taiwan, we also collect other reliable
peer-reviewed articles on Google Scholar and
read them carefully and record their details. And
after we collected data
we start to wash and certificate data
and this step took.
One of my summer vacations last year
I totally had this step very much
but it's quite important for the further
analyzing. And after washing data.
We got a raw dataset and started to use our software
to check our relationship between the variables
and build linear regression models for
estimating regular target variables as output of
the first layer. And following this
we estimate divergent variables via random
forest with sampling assembled algorithms.
And because it's like a random forest wandering in
a highly dimension space
so we named it wandering through the random forest
algorithm
, and the random forest.
It's a kind of a simple machine learning method
and because our data is tiny and have a lot of
missing values
it has a good ability to remove the collinearity
and prevent the result become overfitting. At the
beginning, we wrote the draft. I used the term in
simple hybrid approach, but.
Kobashi sense and molecular sense don't think it
is simple enough
so I use the concept that molecular sense provided
in a seminar.
And we emphasize that if independent variables
and target variables have a good relationship
with each other
then we use linear regression model as an output.
And if the linear regression models can't
estimate them, it will that wandering through the
random forest to give an output. And if above
methods still can't provide the values of
estimation, it will use the climatological
Tables to give an output. It can at least ensure
that the accuracy of the output result is high.
Also, the precision sometimes might be
relevantly low.
And now we talk about the detail of linear
regression models. We operate Pearson
correlations testing between all variables in
raw dataset, and if p value is below zero point zero
one between two variables
then make simple linear regression model. Then.
After we explained the linear regression
the output will going into the second layer
and second layer the random forest and the gap
sampling will treat them. and
Let let me explain what is random forest. Random
forest is an assemble method of many
classification and the regression trees based on
randomly bagging and form the new vectors
randomly.
And the raw data will be divided into train set at
sixty three point two five percent and the test set
at thirty six point seven five percent for out of
bag test.
And if the error rate over fifty percent
then the forest will not output values. And this
method is brilliant to solve the collinearity.
And I think you may have a question now
What is country?
Country is the abbreviation of the
classification and regression tree models. If we
want to make our tree models
we need to select the optimal segmentation
variable J and the segmentation point S. And the
formula seems like rather unfriendly. Then we
describe that more below.
I want to make a simple case. I assumed the data
sheet like this. The simple data recorded three
studies cited in Japan and two in Korea
two in Taiwan.
If we choose say a country
there will be three different divided types. The
types one is R one as in Korea and R two as in Japan and
Taiwan. And the type two is R one as in Japan and R two
as in Korea and in Taiwan. And the type three is R one
as in Taiwan and R two.
Us in Japan or in Korea
and if we use the mean annual temperature to choose
the best divided type, then we get to.
Calculate each group's mean square errors and
then find the minimized mean square errors
combination. And the type one mean square error is
fifty nine. And the same as above
the type two's mean square error will be ninety
seven. And the type three's mean square error is
around eighteen.
So after that, we found the type three is the
minimum MSE and it is the best divided structure.
And repeat the procedure until all variables have
been classified. And then we made the country
models. And if we assemble replicated result
together, it will called random forest. So
following this
I would like to talk about what is Gibbs sampling.
It is.
The Markov chain Monte Carlo algorithms for
obtain the sequence of observations which are
approximately from a specified multivariate
probability distribution when direct sampling
is quite difficult
and I still do not know what that was. And I read a lot
of papers and conclude that in a simple concept
below.
So, if our estimating values are not the number can
be observed, they are existing in possibility in
the undimension obtained by independent
variables, and if we observe a lot of times under
the law of large number
we will get a highest possibility of expected
value in the end, but.
It will cost huge calculating resources. It may
take a few years to get in the result. Hence
we use the Gibbs sampling and then do the
iterations until the result coverage.
We are low of large numbers
and I described it in a more intuitive way
and give sampling fixed variables x one zero
and operate the random forest model to predict the
x one zero, and the missing value in the x one
variables is predicted.
As the V one and the X one zero become X one one
and then fix X two zero
and make another random forest model to predict
the two zero, and the round once process from the X
one to X n is an iteration. In this study
we did the ten to two hundred iterations. So
combine the random forest and give simply. I
subconclude the models.
Framework. After wash the raw data
we build a simple linear regression models for
estimate target variables which have a high
correlation to independent variables. Then use
the Gibbs sampling of each variables and every
independent variables take turns.
As dependent variables for iteration
and each dependent variables will be imputed
missing values by random forest model assembled.
They choose the row and the column as the new small
vectors.
For country models temporarily
then after iteration of Gibbs sampling
every random forest model came out an subset
and then assembled those subset as output for the
second layer in knife set approach
and to compare the simple algorithms with IPCC's
tier one method using broadleaf forest
parameters, five indices were considered.
They are mean absolute percentage error and root
mean square error
and mean square error and mean error. Okay
now we start the so the discussion for carbon stock
and sinks are usually estimated by regression
models, and regression models work well for above
ground carbon stocks and sinks.
But are relevant the effect for below ground part
and this mainly because the relationship between
the independent variables and independent
variables are commonly chaotic or divergent and
appear everywhere in nature ecosystems. There
is.
Large variability in belowground CCS estimated
amount sites and high estimate uncertainties
which can be attributed to environmental and
anthropogenic factors such as temperature
precipitation, soil chemical properties
and biotic communities.
Nutrient availabilities, management intensity
and ecosystem
productivity—something like that.
And bamboo forests are one of types of terrestrial
ecosystem. In different climate
classifications
will have totally different amount of the carbon
stock and sinks because they have the resin system
and can transport the carbon hydrate to other
places and support the youngs of or new root
development.
So they have a more higher characteristic
in their study site in their habit and above ground
carbon have a significant correlation with basal
area and is quite suit for constructing linear
regression to estimate the above ground biomass
and Okuda, since
in 2006 also made.
This kind of linear model to estimate the muscle
bamboos above ground biomass in Japan as well
and we also found the hydrotroughic respiration
have a significant correlation with the NPP.
And a slight significant correlation with
litterfall mass. Perhaps it means that if
microbiome communities in soil decompose
organic matter supply during litterfall
increase, and then nutrient supply to.
Most of bamboo
it will cause most of bamboo's NPP increase or
total nutrient in soil drive the activity of
microbiome to activate the N cycles
ammonifications and nitrifications
and cause the heterotrophic respiration has been
driven as well. However, just only two
peer-reviewed study recorded total.
Nutrient in soil and heterotrophic respiration
at the same study site in China
and the MPP just have a slight significant
correlation with the total nutrient in soil
and the observations number is only three
two in this study and one in China. The
relationship between the soil nutrient
heterotrophic respiration MPP has potential.
For discovering the insight in the future
and below ground net primary production has a
significant correlation with deep net
production. Perhaps it implies that the more
leaves form, the more root and the rhizome grows
because most of bamboo's leaves produce sugars
and supply for developing roots and the rhizome.
The table revealed the performance of ninth set
approach, and the approach is better than the
IPCC's T1 methods using broadleaf forest
parameters in all of the indices. And from the
, sorry
, so sorry, and.
Because the IPCC set was above ground carbon
below ground carbon
and the total carbon stocks have a lower
performance than the knife set approach
and in this kind of figure, the
y-axis is the observations value.
And the x axis is the estimation value, and the MPP
B MPP, and the T MPP. Even though the result seems
not so good for the life cycle approach proved
but is still better than the IPCC's type one
methods. And I think perhaps we needed to collect
more nutrient data from the other study sites.
Because it's very lack of this kind data nowadays
in the most of the forest in the world. And after we
did the ten cross validations
we also operate the holdout data set to make the
holdout testing
and the performance is very similar with the ten
cross validation
which means there is no overfitting of the NAFSET
approach and of the.
Performance is better than the IPCC's tier one
method. Okay, so.
Through the collecting lots of bamboo data
worldwide and the operating Pearson's
correlations, we found the aboveground carbon
stocks and the basal area have a high correlation
to each other. And NPP and the leaf net production
also have this kind of phenomenal. And the NPP and
the heterotrophic respiration.
Or total nutrient in soil have a correlation with
each other as well in the philostachy edulis
stands, and the performance of the said approach
is better than borderly forest perimeters using
the IPCC guideline for estimating carbon stocks
and sinks in philostachy edulis stands
and we believe the KS approach.
Also, can be applied in other forests if the
dataset is reliable
. Thanks for your attention.